Guide to the Billboard Photograph Collection ca 1918-1934 PR 5
New-York Historical Society
Billboard Photograph Collection
ca 1918-1934
New-York Historical Society
PR 5
6 Linear feet (17 boxes)
The photographs appear to have been taken to record which advertisers bought billboard space at 13 sites in Manhattan and two sites in the Bronx, New York City. The views focus on signs but also show surrounding buildings, elevated railroads, and street activity at such heavily traveled intersections as Broadway and Seventh Avenue (Times Square), Fifth Avenue at 42nd Street, Sixth Avenue at 27th Street, Eight Avenue at 110th Street, 125th Street in Harlem, and Third Avenue at 166th Street in the Bronx. The same sites appear repeatedly, sometimes monthly, during the 1920s and into the Great Depression. The photographs reveal changes in both the neighborhoods and in the advertising for many products, among them Chesterfield cigarettes, Wrigley's chewing gum, and Pepsodent toothpaste. The Billboard Photograph Collection is digitized and available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
Access Restrictions
Available by advance appointment only. To schedule an appointment, contact the Print Room Librarian at printroom@nyhistory.org. Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to twenty exposures of stable, unbound material per day. (Researchers may not accrue unused copy amounts from previous days.)
Biographical/Historical Note
The photographs in this collection were taken by the New York City photographic company Drucker & Baltes for the General Outdoor Advertising Company; a billboard company formed in 1925 through the merger of the Fulton Group and Thomas Cusack Company.
Outdoor advertising, in the form of flyers, broadsheets and posters, has existed as long as printing on paper has been economically viable. Large chromolithographed posters were popular in America after the process was introduced in 1840, and were used to advertise circuses and shows, as well as for troop recruitment during the United States Civil War. These posters were generally pasted or hung on the sides of buildings or other structures.
Starting in the 1870s and 1880s, large advertising posters began to appear in American cities along elevated railroads and streets, and the first companies leasing outdoor advertising space were formed. 1896 saw the publication of an industry journal, The Bill Poster, as more money was being made through advertising. In 1900, a standard size of poster (16 sheets of 42" x 28" each), as well as a standard size board on which to place it, was adopted by the burgeoning industry.
As automobiles grew in popularity, outdoor advertising became much more prolific. In New York City, the largest billboards were seen in busy intersections such as Times Square and 42nd St. at 6th Avenue, as well as along elevated railroad tracks.
Such large scale advertising was not welcomed by all. In New York, citizens and politicians complained about the visual pollution they felt billboards added to the cityscape. By 1918, New York City laws restricted billboards from residential areas.
Scope and Contents Note
The Billboard Photograph Collection consists of 226 glass and 677 film negatives which document advertising billboards at 13 Manhattan and two Bronx locations between 1918 and 1934.
Photographers photographed the same sites repeatedly, even when no advertisements appeared on the billboards. In addition to advertisements pasted on large billboards, ads for stores, films, and products were painted on the sides of buildings and are shown in smaller size posters along elevated railroad stations and on street kiosks.
The Manhattan intersections shown are Sixth Ave. & 27th St.; Times Square, Eighth Ave. & 110th St. (Cathedral Parkway); Fifth Ave. & 42nd St.; Sixth Ave. between 42nd & 43rd Sts.; Sixth Ave. & 44th St.; Sixth Ave. & 47th St.; Seventh Ave & 34th St.; Seventh Ave & 42nd St.; Madison Ave., between Fifth & Sixth Aves.; Eighth Ave. & 58th St.; Broadway & 57th St.; and 125th St. between Seventh and Lenox Aves. The Bronx locations are 166th St. & Third Ave. and Willis Ave. near 148th St. Photographs in the finding aid are identified by location; for additional information about products advertised and buildings depicted, refer to the digitized images. Indices by business, product advertised, theater and production are also available in the Collection File at the repository.
The same billboards were photographed repeatedly and show changes in product names, advertising methods, and slogans. Many products and companies advertised here continue to be in business in 2001. In addition to billboards, many businesses and buildings are shown in each shot, and these also change over the years. The Publicity Building, at the junction of 7th Avenue, Broadway, and 47th St., was photographed from different angles, allowing changes in the businesses housed within it to be tracked. This turnover is especially notable during the Depression years, when many firms failed or moved to different locations.
Billboards advertise the following categories of products: real estate; political campaigns and candidates; fundraising campaigns; banks; clothing; beverages; food products; tobacco; automobile and gasoline companies; film and theater productions and venues; restaurants and hotels; services, such as swimming and dancing schools; and other products, such as pencils and magazines. Among the best-represented products in the collection are Wrigley's Spearmint Gum, Camel Cigarettes, Union Dime Savings Bank and Armour Star Ham.
The 1920s witnessed the introduction of film industry advertising. Ads for individual movies, as well as for movie theaters, film production companies, and film sound technologies, are well represented in this collection. Films and movie theaters, as well as plays and other entertainment events (such as rodeos at Madison Square Garden) are noted within the database. Notable productions include the first sound film The Jazz Singer and Mae West's play Diamond Lil.
Billboards advertise candidates for elected office, most often in party tickets. Slogans like "Vote for Hoover and Ottinger. Continue prosperity. Vote every arrow" or "Smith and Robinson. Vote every star" appeared during the 1928 election season. The previous fall, voters had been urged to pay attention to constitutional amendments and decent housing, and to "vote no on number 6, separate state and federal elections in interest of good government" and "vote yes on all the others, more subways, improved living conditions, better state government."
Real estate, both in New York City and the surrounding areas, was also heavily promoted on billboards. Tudor City was advertised upon its completion, starting in 1927. Signs touting auctions for land or property in the Bronx and Long Island are also pictured. In addition, many signs sold Florida (or, specific cities, such as Palm Beach) as a vacation spot. These advertisements were often paid for by travel agents, although some ads for Miami were attributed to the Miami Chamber of Commerce.
During the years of the Depression in the 1930s, billboards advertising relief efforts and committees appeared, mostly in space donated by billboard companies. These signs urged New Yorkers to donate time and money to help out those less fortunate, or advertised committees formed to help the impoverished.
Before prohibition of alcohol (the Eighteenth Amendment) was enacted in 1920, a few billboards and painted signs advertised beer and liquor. Prohibition's repeal in 1933 saw a huge increase in advertising on the part of beer companies. Prepared food (such as Mueller's Cooked Spaghetti) first appears in advertising around 1928.
Arrangement Note
The negatives are arranged as they were received, by negative number, in a chronological run. Item number refers to this negative number. Indices to products advertised, dates, and locations of billboards are available on-site in the collection file, and refer to these negative numbers.
Provenance
Purchase, 1982.
Existence and Location of Copies
The Billboard Photograph Collection is digitized and available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
Times Square (New York, N.Y.); New York (N.Y.) -- Buildings, structures, etc.; Advertising; Advertising -- Chewing gum; Advertising -- Cigarettes; Advertising -- Toothpaste; Billboards; Signs and signboards; Streets -- New York (State) -- New York.; Black-and-white negatives; Glass negatives; Negatives; Broadway (New York, N.Y.); Bronx (New York, N.Y.); Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)
- 5th Ave & 42nd billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 7732 (Box 1, Item 59610)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave, c. 1918-1919; 7801 (Box 1, Item 59611)
- Willis near E. 148th, c. 1919 (Box 1, Item 59612)
- 5th Ave & 42nd, c. 1918 (Box 1, Item 59613)
- 5th Ave & 42nd, c. 1920-1921; 4250 (Box 1, Item 59614)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboard by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59615)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Elevated railway in front of billboards, billboard by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59616)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboard by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1921 (Box 1, Item 59617)
- Willis near E. 148th, c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59618)
- 6th Ave & 44th, c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59619)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59620)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920-1921 (Box 1, Item 59621)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59622)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59623)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1919-1920 (Box 1, Item 59624)
- 5th Ave & 42nd, c. 1919-1920 (Box 1, Item 59625)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboard by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59626)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave, c. 1918-1919 (Box 1, Item 59627)
- 6th Ave & 47th, c. 1918-1919 (Box 1, Item 59628)
- 8th Ave & 110th, c. 1919 or before (Box 1, Item 59629)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboard by Realty Advance & Supply Company, c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59630)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboard by Thos. Cusack Company (Box 1, Item 59631)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx), c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59632)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboard by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1919-1920 (Box 1, Item 59633)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboard by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1921 (Box 1, Item 59634)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboard by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1919-1920 (Box 1, Item 59635)
- Willis near E. 148th Billboard by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1919 (Box 1, Item 59636)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboard by Realty Advance & Supply Company, c. 1918 (Box 1, Item 59637)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboard by Thos. Cusack Company, October, 1919 (Box 1, Item 59638)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboard by Thos. Cusack Company, October, 1919 (Box 1, Item 59639)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboard by Thos. Cusack Company, October, 1919 (Box 1, Item 59640)
- Madison, between 59th and 60th, c. 1919 (Box 1, Item 59641)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Bilboards by Realty Advance Co., c. 1920 (Box 1, Item 59642)
- 5th Ave & 42nd, c. 1918-1920 (Box 2, Item 59643)
- 7th Ave & 42nd, c. 1919-1920 (Box 2, Item 59644)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboard by Realty Advance Company (Box 2, Item 59645)
- 7th Ave & 42nd, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59646)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, c. 1920 (Box 2, Item 59647)
- 5th Ave & 42nd, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59648)
- Madison, between 59th and 60th, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59649)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Empty Billboard by Realty Advance Company, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59650)
- 7th Ave & 34th, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59651)
- NO NEGATIVE BY THIS NUMBER (Box 2, Item 59652)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Top of negative masked, billboards by Realty Advance Company, c. 1919-1920 (Box 2, Item 59653)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Realty Advance System, c. 1919 - 1920 (Box 2, Item 59654)
- 8th Ave & 58th Billboards by Realty Advance System, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59655)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Realty Advance System, c. 1919 - 1920 (Box 2, Item 59656)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Realty Advance System, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59657)
- Broadway & 57th, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59658)
- Broadway & 57th, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59659)
- Madison, between 59th and 60th, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59660)
- 6th Ave & 47th, c. 1918 (Box 2, Item 59661)
- 8th Ave & 110th Taken from "El," train appears in picture, billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1921 (Box 2, Item 59662)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, c. 1921 (Box 2, Item 59663)
- 5th Ave & 42nd, c. 1920 - 1921 (Box 2, Item 59664)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboard by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1921 (Box 2, Item 59665)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboard by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1920 - 1921 (Box 2, Item 59666)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboard by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59667)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox, c. 1919 (Box 2, Item 59668)
- Willis near E. 148th, c. 1920 (Box 2, Item 59669)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1919 - 1920 (Box 2, Item 59670)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1920 (Box 2, Item 59671)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1919 - 1920 (Box 2, Item 59672)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1920 (Box 2, Item 59673)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59674)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59675)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59676)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Compnay, c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59677)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1919 - 1920 (Box 3, Item 59678)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1919 - 1920 (Box 3, Item 59679)
- Willis near E. 148th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1921 (Box 3, Item 59680)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1919 - 1920 (Box 3, Item 59681)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59682)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, c. 1921 (Box 3, Item 59683)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox, September, c. 1919 (Box 3, Item 59684)
- 8th Ave & 110th Taken from "El" looking SW, billboards by Thos. Cusack Company, c. 1921 (Box 3, Item 59685)
- 6th Ave & 44th, c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59686)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59687)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59688)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59689)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1921 (Box 3, Item 59690)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1919 - 1920 (Box 3, Item 59691)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59692)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 - 1921 (Box 3, Item 59693)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx), c. 1919 (Box 3, Item 59694)
- Willis near E. 148th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 (Box 3, Item 59695)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., c. 1920 - 1921 (Box 3, Item 59696)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59697)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59698)
- 8th Ave & 110th Taken from "El," looking SW, billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59699)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59700)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., construction in foreground - maybe the digging of a subway tunnel?, May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59701)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Bryant Park in foreground, billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59702)
- Willis near E. 148th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59703)
- 5th Ave & 42nd, May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59704)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59705)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59706)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59707)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 3, Item 59708)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 4, Item 59709)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 4, Item 59710)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 4, Item 59711)
- 6th Ave & 44th, May 1920 (Box 4, Item 59712)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 4, Item 59713)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, May 1920 (Box 4, Item 59714)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 4, Item 59715)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May 1920 (Box 4, Item 59716)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59717)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59718)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59719)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59720)
- 6th Ave & 44th, 1921 (Box 4, Item 59721)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboard by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59722)
- 8th Ave & 110th Taken from "El," looking SW; billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59723)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59724)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59725)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59726)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59727)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59728)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59729)
- Willis near E. 148th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59730)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59731)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 (Box 4, Item 59732)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 4, Item 59733)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 4, Item 59734)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 4, Item 59735)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co.; are blank, August, 1921 (Box 4, Item 59736)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 4, Item 59737)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 4, Item 59738)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 4, Item 59739)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co.; all blank, August, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59740)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59741)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59742)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59743)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59744)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59745)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59746)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., August, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59747)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59748)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59749)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59750)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59751)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59752)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59753)
- Willis near E. 148th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59754)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59755)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59756)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59757)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59758)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59759)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59760)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59761)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59762)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59763)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., December, 1921 (Box 5, Item 59764)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 5, Item 59765)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 5, Item 59766)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 5, Item 59767)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 5, Item 59768)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co.; one billboard being changed is shown, 1921 or 1922 (Box 5, Item 59769)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 5, Item 59770)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 5, Item 59771)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 5, Item 59772)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 5, Item 59773)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 6, Item 59774)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 6, Item 59775)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1921 or 1922 (Box 6, Item 59776)
- Willis near E. 148th Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1922 (Box 6, Item 59777)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1922 (Box 6, Item 59778)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co., 1922 (Box 6, Item 59779)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack & Co.; view of Bryant Park, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59780)
- 8th Ave & 110th Taken from "El," looking SW; billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1922 (Box 6, Item 59781)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1922 (Box 6, Item 59782)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1922 (Box 6, Item 59783)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59784)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59785)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59786)
- 8th Ave & 110th Taken from "El," looking SW; billboards by This. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59787)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59788)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59789)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59790)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59791)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59792)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59793)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59794)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., January, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59795)